== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(phone line ringing)
(Amy(on skype):)Hi, Sheldon. What's up?
Well, I'm calling
(Sheldon:)because Thanksgiving
is coming up,
(Sheldon:)and I wanted to offer you
the aquarium tickets.
(Amy:)No one can go with you?
(Sheldon:)No. They'd rather spend
the holiday with each other
(Sheldon:)than find out of this is the
year I finally touch a starfish.
(Sheldon:)Anyway,
I wouldn't want
(Sheldon:)the tickets to go to waste,
so take whomever you'd like.
(Howard:)Oh.
(Amy:)Okay. Thank you.
And feel free
(Sheldon:)to tell your guest
that the Myanmar catfish
(Sheldon:)is also known
as the pilgrim fish.
(Sheldon:)In case the turkey's dry
and you need something juicy.
(Amy(on skype):)Sheldon...
I can tell you want to go,
(Amy:)so if you'd be comfortable
with it,
(Amy:)maybe we could go as friends.
(Sheldon:)You don't think
that will be awkward?
Well... it is Thanksgiving
in an aquarium cafeteria,
(Amy:)so I'm gonna go out
on a limb here and say yes.
But if you mean between us...